Justin Samuel Wright

8353 W Myrtle Avenue, Glendale, AZ 85305 (623) 826-7073 Jswright91@gmail.com

Career Objective

Web Developer / Computer Repair technician with 2+ years' experience working for a local warehouse. Broad knowledge of Windows, and Linux environments. Interested in pursuing an Entry Level Web Development, Web Design, Graphics Design, or Computer Repair position.

Educational Summary

Glendale Community College, Phoenix, AZ

AA Business / BA(in progress) Computer Information Systems, August 2009-Present Courses Include: First-Year Composition, College Algebra/Functions, Brief Calculus, Rock Music & Culture, Psychology & Culture, Survey Computer Information Systems, Microeconomic Principles, and Macroeconomic Principles, Legal

Ethical/Regulatory Issues in Business and Finite Mathmatics.

Sandra Day O'Connor High School, Phoenix, AZ General Education, August 2005 – May 2009 Diploma

Work Experience

06/2012 – Present Web Developer/ Browns Partsmaster

Manages and writes code for the website. [CSS, HTML, Jquery, MySQL, PHP] Takes Pictures, and Designs all Images for the product merchandise. Maintains stock of new supplies and computer components for the company. Diagnoses problems with website, and computers in use.

02/2011 – 08/2011 Easy Tech Resident / Staples

Diagnose and repair customer's computers and tech devices.

Assist customers in purchasing tech and business management products.

Replacing major components in customer's computers.

Responsible for the well-being of all the computers carried within the tech-department.

Consult with customers with their copy needs.

Operating the copy machines, taking and completing customer orders.

Diagnosing occasional printer problems, and computer issues.

Assisting customers with their projects in the 'self-service' center.

06/2009 -- 09/2010 Hourly Manager/ Burger King

Responsible for restaurant operations, including opening & closing restaurant.

Directed, trained team members.

Motivated team members to comply with loss control procedures.

Completed checklists and procedures for cash reporting, and inventory control.

Justin Samuel Wright

References

[References are available on request.]